<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on LiveFitt</title>
    <link>https://livefitt.net/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on LiveFitt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://livefitt.net/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Decoding Fitness Efficiency: The Stimulus to Fatigue Ratio</title>
      <link>https://livefitt.net/posts/stimulus-fatigue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://livefitt.net/posts/stimulus-fatigue/</guid>
      <description>Unveiling the Efficiency Equation In the pursuit of fitness excellence, efficiency is the silent architect of progress. One key concept that often takes center stage in this efficiency narrative is the Stimulus to Fatigue Ratio. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the intricacies of this ratio, deciphering how it holds the key to maximizing gains while minimizing the toll on your body.&#xA;The Stimulus to Fatigue Ratio Explained At its core, the Stimulus to Fatigue Ratio is a measure of the effectiveness of a workout in relation to the fatigue it induces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying Fitness Periodization: Unveiling the Power of Micro, Macro, and Mesocycles</title>
      <link>https://livefitt.net/posts/periodization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://livefitt.net/posts/periodization/</guid>
      <description>The Symphony of Fitness Progression In the intricate symphony of fitness, periodization takes center stage, orchestrating the harmonious progression of strength, endurance, and overall performance. Let&amp;rsquo;s unravel the layers of this musical journey—microcycles, macrocycles, and mesocycles—each playing a distinct yet interconnected role in the grand composition of physical transformation.&#xA;Understanding the Rhythms: Microcycles Microcycles, akin to the notes in a musical piece, represent the shortest duration in periodization. Typically spanning a week, these cycles break down the intricacies of training into daily nuances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Minimalist Training: A Deep Dive into Maximum Results</title>
      <link>https://livefitt.net/posts/minimalist-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://livefitt.net/posts/minimalist-training/</guid>
      <description>Navigating Success Through Simplicity In the ever-evolving landscape of fitness, a paradigm shift is underway—the resurgence of minimalist training. This approach champions simplicity, urging enthusiasts to focus on essential elements that promise maximum results. It&amp;rsquo;s not a journey of shortcuts but a strategic odyssey centered around what genuinely matters in the pursuit of fitness goals.&#xA;Unpacking the Principles of Minimalist Training Minimalist training finds its strength in compound movements that engage multiple muscle groups concurrently.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
